<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollViewExercise</string>
    <string name="alan_turing" translatable="false">"Alan Turing é considerado o pai da computação, tendo desenvolvido sistemas e conceitos que serviram de base para a tecnologia atual.           Ele trabalhou para a inteligência britânica durante a Segunda Guerra Mundial, com o objetivo de traduzir textos nazistas, e criou a inteligência artificial.           Alan Turing nasceu em 23 de junho de 1912, na cidade de Paddington, na Inglaterra. Ele era filho de um funcionário do Serviço Civil indiano, Julius Mathison, e Ethel Sara Stoney.           Com grande facilidade em matemática aos 15 anos, Turing resolveu problemas complexos sem nunca ter estudado cálculo. Aos 19 anos formou-se em matemática pela Universidade de Cambridge, pronto para iniciar uma trajetória que se perpetua por gerações. "</string>
    <string name="john_von_newmann">"The complexity is partly due to the existence of many sources of information, some of which are inaccessible, others which are at variance or controversial. However, the main cause of this complexity is the richness of von Neumann's contributions. Its spectrum includes several areas of Mathematics, Applied Mathematics, Physics, Meteorology, Economics and Computing. In many cases, his contributions went far beyond solving problems proposed by others, opening up new areas of research and launching new problems. Very personal description of von Neumann's contributions was made by his friends and collaborators Ulam (1958) and Halmos (1973). Various works dedicated to von Neumann's contributions can be found in the special issue of the journal Annals of the History of Computing, as well as in the Proceedings of an American Mathematical Society symposium (Glimm et al., 1990b) held in 1990. The environment in which von Neumann was raised and educated is described by his brother Nicholas A. Vonneuman     "</string>
    <string name="title">Grandes cientistas da area da computação</string>
</resources>